

# Ilir Perolli

Nationality: Kosovar

(+383) 44547565

Date of birth: 20/07/1999

**Gender:** Male

**■ Email address:** ilir perolli@live.com

**Website:** <u>amici.epizy.com</u>

**Website:** <u>bufi.epizy.com</u>

**Website:** uniworks.epizy.com

Github: : <a href="https://github.com/llirPerolli">https://github.com/llirPerolli</a>

• Address: 9 Nentori nr.11, 50000 Gjakove (Kosovo)

#### **ABOUT ME**

Innovative web developer with 5 years of experience in the front-end and 3 years in the backend with PHP language. 1 year of experience with Data Science using Python. General knowledge in technologies such as: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, Object Oriented PHP, Laravel, JAVA, Python, Bootstrap, SQL, MySQL. Talented in project management, team leadership and independent problem solving.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### **Bachelor**

Public University of Prizren "Ukshin Hoti" [ 01/10/2017 - 17/09/2020 ]

Address: Rruga e Shkronjave, 20000 Prizren (Kosovo)

uni-prizren.com

#### Master

Public University of Prizren "Ukshin Hoti" [ 01/11/2020 - Current ]

Address: Rruga e Shkronjave, 20000 Prizren (Kosovo)

uni-prizren.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Instructor

**Digital School** [ 03/11/2020 – 30/06/2021 ]

City: Gjakove Country: Kosovo

Programming instructor (Html, CSS, Javascript, PHP and MySQL, Wordpress) for age groups from 16 to 18 years old and (Code, Scratch, App Inventor) instructor for age groups from 7 to 15 years old.

# Web programmer

EGED (Entrepreneurship, Growth and Economic Development) - NGO [ 01/07/2019 - 10/01/2020 ]

City: Gjakove Country: Kosovo

Development and management of EGED websites and social networks, planning and designing projects related to programming and website development.

### **PROJECTS**

#### **Amici**

Amici is a platform that enables users (mostly students) to access books and lectures making it easier for them to attend computer science classes. Literature in Amici account is divided based on the academic year in which the student is. Students can also exchange files (seminar papers, projects, photographs, etc.) of various kinds. Another option is to post the videos via the link, where the student first creates a folder by naming it (eg: "Lessons from Java") and then adds the videos to the folder by naming them first and placing the link. Among other things, students can communicate with each other through messages (chat), where they can discuss various topics or post a picture.

http://amici.epizy.com/

#### Bufi

Bufi enables users (simple user or company) to post products or offer services on the web application. The post gives the name and description of the product as well as its price. Finally select the category, city and upload the photos for that product. Those products can then be viewed by other users, searched and users can follow each other in order for their posts to appear on the front page, without losing any product. The profiles of each business or ordinary user can also be viewed, with the possibility for another user to see all the products.

### bufi.epizy.com

### **EmployingX**

EmployingX offers professional personnel services at the highest level. It specializes in finding professional, trustworthy and affordable personnel that will work remotely for any company. Companies will not need to directly hire the employees in this platform and as such will not have any labour obligations towards them. The employees can register on platform and upload their CVs, companies can register too and create jobs, and the administrator's job is to assign the employee to the company suitable for that job.

http://employingx.epizy.com/

#### **OpenBci controlling Dobot**

OpenBCI stands for open-source brain-computer interface (BCI). In this project the electrical activity of body is sampled. The versatile and affordable biosensing systems are being used to sample electrical brain activity (EEG) to being able to more the robot called Dobot. The direction of Dobot is changed by blinking the eyes and the move is realized by concentrating and converting all the electrical brain activity in coordinates for Dobot.

https://github.com/llirPerolli/OpenBCI/tree/master/OpenBCI Tutorials-master/EMG Controlled Dobot

### **News Detector**

In this project is made a simple news detector using Naive Bayes algorithm, which is a machine learning model that are a family of simple "probabilistic classifiers" based on applying Bayes' theorem with strong independence assumptions between the features. This classifier can detect news from different categories such as: sports, politics, health and economics.

https://github.com/IlirPerolli/DataScienceProjects/tree/master/NaiveBayesNewsDetector

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): **Albanian** 

Other language(s):

# **English**

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1** 

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

HTML / CSS / Bootstrap / PHP / SQL / MySQL / Java / Laravel / Javascript / Python

#### **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

# First Place in Open ICT education for youth employment

Open Data Kosovo [ 27/01/2020 ]

Open ICT education for youth employment

### **PHP** with Laravel

Udemy [ 05/09/2020 ]

PHP with Laravel for beginners - Become a master in laravel

# Javascript & jQuery

Udemy [ 22/10/2020 ]

Javascript & jQuery - Certification Course for Beginners

# **Techstitution 4.0**

Open Data Kosovo [ 11/11/2020 ]

Techstitution 4.0 Certificate of training